<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo minimalist SPA</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo minimalist SPA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/1-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/1-about/</guid>
      <description>Hugo minimalist SPA 
A minimalist single page application theme for Hugo, with a clear focus on responsiveness, simplicity and elegance.
About I love challenges, and making a single page application using Hugo, a static site generator, seemed like a good one. The SPA core is made using plain Javascript (only JQuery is used for the Ajax requests). I aim to provide a simple but powerful design anyone can use, either for personal or professional matters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distribution</title>
      <link>/3-distribution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/3-distribution/</guid>
      <description>Distribution License
This project is licensed under the MIT License - see the LICENSE file for details.
Contributing If you want to contribute to this theme, you can make a pull request and I will be glad to check it out.
Versioning You can modify this theme as much as you want. If you want to distribute a modified version, you must publish a link to this repository indicating that I&amp;rsquo;m the original author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to use</title>
      <link>/2-howtouse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2-howtouse/</guid>
      <description>How to use (MUST READ)
This is not the usual Hugo theme you can download and start adding contents right away. But don&#39;t get scared, you won&#39;t need to read all this document in order to create your site. Unless you aim to create something very customized, you just need to read the basics. Making the theme a SPA comes with some essential features you need to know before starting to build your website.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>